{
    "subject": "resource/Josiah_Duane_Hicks",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Wales",
    "human_readable": "Josiah Duane Hicks was born in Wales.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.97440505027771,
            "question": "What is the significance of Josiah Duane Hicks being born in Wales?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9142007231712341,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the culture in Wales during Josiah Duane Hicks's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9095945358276367,
            "question": "Where was Josiah Duane Hicks born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.699567437171936,
            "question": "Were there any notable events associated with Josiah Duane Hicks's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.62606281042099,
            "question": "What country is Josiah Duane Hicks from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45111480355262756,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Josiah Duane Hicks's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3806826174259186,
            "question": "Is there any information about Josiah Duane Hicks's later life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3762035369873047,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Josiah Duane Hicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36901673674583435,
            "question": "Are there any historical records related to Josiah Duane Hicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2870337665081024,
            "question": "What is known about Josiah Duane Hicks's life and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Josiah Duane Hicks was born in Wales.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3956_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical records related to Josiah Duane Hicks?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3956_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Josiah Duane Hicks?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3956_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Josiah Duane Hicks's later life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3956_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3956_36.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Josiah Duane Hicks was born in Wales, as mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3956/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3956/re-ranker-msmarco/22.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Josiah Duane Hicks was born in Machen, Monmouthshire, Wales, on August 1, 1844. Therefore, the statement that Josiah Duane Hicks was born in Wales is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}